(This story is entirely fictional)
You messed up on the last big question.
You did it on purpose, right?
If you hadn't done it on purpose,
(Based on Doctor Qin: Executer)
our scores would've tied.
We still could've gotten
into the same university.
But...
But what?
But you lost this time.
You owe me a soda.
Let's go.
Wait.
Come back.
Closer.
(Setting Off Fireworks)
Qin.
Jin Keke definitely
isn't coming tonight.
Set them off.
(Qin Ming.)
(It's your turn to solve it.)
(Solve it now.)
(Qin Ming.)
=Doctor Qin: Executer=
=Episode 8=
(Weiyou Mart)
Welcome.
Three yuan.
What?
You clearly came looking for me.
Why make that face?
You know I work here.
Are you always on night shifts?
The schedule's right there.
If you've got questions,
look for yourself.
Before, you said
you've been having the same dream
for ten years,
and you'd tell me when we met again.
Sorry.
I don't wanna answer that right now.
Then can you tell me
why you never replied
to that last letter ten years ago?
A reply?
From the day I dropped out,
my life was already over.
You probably don't know
how hard it is for a girl to survive.
Sometimes, I think
being dead would've been fine.
But I survived.
If I hadn't dropped out,
if I had stayed in school with you,
taken the Gaokao with you,
and gone to university with you,
maybe
I could've had the life I wanted.
But there's no "if."
About why Xia Wen ended up like that,
I've been thinking for ten years.
You said
I always leave without saying goodbye.
Maybe
I just didn't have the strength
to say goodbye.
Sorry.
I didn't come here
to pick at your scars.
But lately, there've been some clues
at crime scenes
that remind me of our past.
If my showing up disturbed you,
I'm sorry.
Qin Ming.
Trust your eyes and your feelings.
Just don't trust the story
anyone tells you.
A pack of cigarettes.
Hello, welcome.
Thirteen yuan.
Okay.
Welcome back anytime.
I'm leaving.
Actually, in a way,
Xia Wen's death gave me a mom.
So the pain isn't as sharp.
(Weiyou Mart)
(Lime Juice)
(Wang Capital Management Co., Ltd.
Old City Redevelopment)
He Guifen.
Your turn.
Mr. Qin.
Mr. Qin?
Qin Ming!
You're spacing out again?
Just get to the point.
Han Liang found info on Xu Meng.
She
left Longfan half a year ago.
But she has a stepmother
living in Jiuyuan Apartments
named He Guifen.
Have you found anything else
on He Guifen?
Not yet.
I heard some things while doing
door-to-door visits.
An old neighbor said
Xu Meng's mom died young.
Her dad died a few years
after marrying He Guifen.
He Guifen didn't kick Xu Meng out,
but she didn't treat
her stepdaughter well.
That's easy to imagine.
Keep digging.
Mainly check
whether He Guifen got connected
to Zhang Xiaodong
because of Xu Meng.
Also, keep looking for Xu Meng.
Got it.
He Guifen!
He Guifen.
Liang.
There's a foul-smelling liquid
leaking out.
Notify the tech team
and the forensic examiner.
Get ready to break the door.
Got it.
Livor mortis is fixed.
Doesn't fade under pressure.
Rigor mortis is easing
from the large joints.
Time of death is around
seventy-two hours ago.
Fibers under her nails.
The skin loss doesn't look severe.
Probably from scratching herself.
Blood spots in the whites of her eyes.
Purple lips.
Hello?
Are you Xu Meng?
You're lying!
What do you want?
You liar!
Give me back my money!
Yeah, I'm calling the police.
I'm gonna have the cops arrest you!
Hypoxia?
Sudden heart attack?
Look at the scratch marks on her chest.
She must've been in terrible heart pain
to scratch herself that hard.
No sign anyone else came in.
The lock's fine too.
Between how she looks
and all these torn-up papers,
she must've found out something
she couldn't handle
and got so worked up
she couldn't breathe.
Found a torn-up contract.
(Jia Xibei)
The seal's fake.
She got scammed?
No wonder she died of anger.
We can only make a preliminary judgment
at the scene.
We'll have to wait for the autopsy
to rule out drugs.
Now Xu Meng's missing,
and He Guifen's dead.
These two things
are very likely connected.
Go check He Guifen's social circle.
What's going on here?
I heard He Guifen's dead.
He Guifen?
You know He Guifen?
No, I don't.
(No Entry; Police)
After him!
Stop running!
Stop!
Over there! After him!
It's flying.
This place is so winding.
Here!
Turn around!
You're really a runner.
Go.
Move!
I think it's this way.
- Move!
- Go.
Liang.
This is the investment contract
He Guifen was holding when she died.
The contract's fake.
And
for this fake contract investment,
He Guifen mortgaged her house.
She got scammed out
of her entire life savings.
No wonder she was so angry.
We need to have a good talk
with the sprinter, Jia Xibei.
You're the contract guarantor?
Officer,
I'm a victim too.
Guifen and I both got scammed.
When I found out I'd been scammed,
I wanted to hurry and tell Guifen.
But then...
Who's Li Mei on this contract?
Oh, Ms. Li.
She's my upline.
She took the money and disappeared.
I can't reach her no matter what.
Where did you meet Li Mei?
Half a year ago.
At Fengshan Villa.
Fengshan Villa?
Half a year ago,
I was delivering a contract
to Le Tianyi.
Mr. Jia?
Hello, I'm Li Mei.
I'm a friend of Mr. Zhang.
Ms. Li, hello.
A friend of Mr. Zhang?
You look so elegant.
What did you want to see me about?
Well,
is He Guifen your client?
Technically,
Guifen is Mr. Zhang's client.
Ms. Li, you're interested?
Let me buy you a drink.
(I did get greedy back then.)
(I figured if I could close)
(He Guifen's contract with Ms. Li,)
(maybe I'd get a bigger cut,)
(so I brought her to meet He Guifen.)
And you are?
Guifen.
Jia,
you're right on time.
Let's talk inside?
Okay.
Guifen.
How come you've lost so much weight
after just a few days?
My bad. Forgot to introduce.
This is our money backer, Ms. Li.
She's from the big city.
Your monthly interest
always came on time,
and that's thanks to Ms. Li.
Ms. Li.
- Ms. He, hello.
- I've heard so much about you.
Hello.
This is your dividend from last quarter.
How about it?
Wasn't I right about investing
in this project?
Yes.
Thank you, Ms. Li.
No worries.
Let me get you some water.
I'll do it.
Don't bother.
Don't be so formal, Ms. He.
We're getting rich together.
Jia told me
you've got a great eye for investment.
Yes.
So as soon as a good project came up,
I came straight to you.
Look.
What good project is it this time?
How much can I make?
Listen,
this project
has a high return rate.
Backed by a big group.
Guaranteed profit.
It's just that the threshold
is a bit high.
Minimum investment
can't be under a million.
Only twenty spots in the whole province.
A million?
I...
Ms. He.
No rush.
Let me tell you, this project
has an annual return of 80%.
In a year, you get back 1.8 million.
And it pays interest quarterly.
That much?
You get back two hundred thousand
every quarter.
I... I wanna make that 1.8 million.
But I only have five hundred thousand.
Five hundred thousand?
- Oh boy.
- I can't come up with a million.
I only have five hundred thousand.
Ms. He.
I've got a suggestion.
Go on.
Your house is in a good location.
Should be worth
over five hundred thousand.
Get a mortgage on it from the bank.
Then you'll have exactly a million.
A year later, you get 1.8 million.
After paying off the loan,
you still net
seven or eight hundred thousand.
I...
Guifen,
you gotta think it over carefully.
I'd say
this is practically
a once-in-a-lifetime chance.
If you invest in this project,
a year from now,
you'll be a millionaire.
I...
But... but I...
Hey, Jia.
Stop talking.
Let Ms. He think it over.
See, it's like this.
I'd love to save you a spot.
But too many people are fighting for it.
If the spots get grabbed up,
there's nothing I can do.
Ms. He, take your time.
No rush.
I'm heading out.
Think it over, Guifen.
Bye.
We're leaving.
I agree!
I'll go do the paperwork right now.
I...
I... I'll go get the deed.
Verified.
Jia Xibei did introduce Le Tianyi
to some loan shark resources
and drinking buddies.
Within Sun Group,
Jia Xibei
is pretty marginalized.
His relationship with Le Tianyi
was all about sucking up to him.
Just to get a bigger cut.
This is the sketch of Li Mei
that Jia Xibei provided.
Way too generic.
There's something even weirder.
Li Mei's account
was stolen from a rural woman.
All the funds went overseas.
No trail left.
(Executer?)
Jia Xibei
definitely knows more
about Zhang Xiaodong.
Han Liang.
Get everything out of him.
Yes, sir!
Didn't you wanna make up
for your crimes?
Fine, here's your chance.
Think hard about what you left out.
My throat feels a bit scratchy.
I don't want water.
Then what do you want?
Give me a cigarette.
Jia Xibei! Are you insane?
Come on.
Sit down.
Calm down.
Talk or not?
Throat hurts. Can't talk.
You're really pushing it, huh?
Wait.
I'll talk.
One time, Le Tianyi got wasted
and was bragging to me.
He said, "Jia Xiba..."
My nickname.
Xiba,
I know a huge secret
about Zhang Xiaodong.
When the time's right,
if things go south, I'll expose it.
You're keeping us in suspense?
Just tell us!
He said
Zhang Xiaodong buried something shady
at Fengshan Villa.
(He once wove lies)
(into the most beautiful "virtue")
(and watered his family's bloodline
with the bones of young girls.)
(Now,)
(his rotting body)
(will become fertilizer
for another field of flowers.)
♪Sunset washes over the old wall♪
♪Milk tea cools on the stone steps♪
♪Sea wind tugs at your sleeve♪
♪Unspoken words just flee and fade♪
♪The marks on the desk
have faded yellow♪
♪I turned around,
and a gunshot rang out♪
♪No one can truly feel another's pain♪
♪The wind is cold,
a fading shadow sways♪
♪Tonight, I don't care
about the universe♪
♪I only want to see this through
with you♪
♪A bullet pierces the spring night♪
♪You sink into the vast crowd♪
♪Years later, when we meet again♪
♪Don't mention this moonlit night♪
♪The waves smooth
two lines of footprints♪
♪Half a cup of sweetness
sinks into the sand♪
♪Tonight, I don't care
about the universe♪
♪I only want to see this through
with you♪
♪Wind back to shore,
clouds back to hills♪
♪We stop here in this night♪
♪This is the past, the only,
the last look back♪
♪One gunshot echoes through half a life♪